

OLUWAKEMI ISOGUN

Experience

14-06-2020-ongoing

Front-End Developer • ACE MEDIA Social Media and Digital Marketing Agency.

20-09-2020 - Ongoing

Front-End Developer • Binary Generation Labs.

25-09-2020 - Ongoing

Web development instructor • Developers Student Club Futa.



No. 19, Samuel Temitope Abu street Harmony Estate, Ajah Lagos state.



08137913553, 09090634698



<u>Oluwakemisola757@gma</u> il.com

Website:

https://kemmie001.github.io/portfolio/Github Profile:



https://github.com/Kem mie001

Linked in:

https://www.linkedin.co m/in/oluwakemi-isogun-187799199/

Education

Federal University of Technology Akure, Ondo state.

- Mechanical Engineering
- Deans' List First Year. First and Second Semester.

Web Development Training.

- Member of the Developers student club.
- Freecodecamp Responsive Web Design Certificate.
- Member of the Microsoft student partner.
- Student at Mobile Web Specialist Google Africa Developers Scholarship 2020.





eadership Roles:

- Senior Prefect in Secondary School.
- Trainer at Code World Tutorial Scheme.
- Volunteered to mentor Beginners at Developers student club
- Team lead at Developers Student Club Futa.

TECHNICAL SKILLS:

- WEB DESIGN
- HTML
- CSS --- BOOTSTRAP, MATERIAL DESIGN
- JAVASCRIPT
- VUE.JS
- FIREBASE

SOFT SKILLS:

- ✓ EXCELLENT TEAM SPIRIT
- ✓ CREATIVE PROBLEM SOLVING
- ✓ TIME MANAGEMENT

Hobbies: Reading, Writing and Coding

I love to read books most especially on how the web works. I also like writing tech contents at my leisure time. Coding is part of me learning new things about the web through coding gives me a special type of joy.

Professional Summary:

Solution-driven professional excelling in highly collaborative work environment, finding solutions to challenges and focused on customer satisfaction. Proven experience developing consumer-focused web sites using HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript, and Vue. Experience building products for desktop, phone and mobile app users, meeting highest standards for web design, user experience, best practices, usability and speed. Also, understanding of Search Engine Optimization and important of SSL certificate to get required consumer audience.

Responding to challenges by designing and developing solutions and



building web applications aligned to customer's services. Translating solutions into code and working across many different APIs, third-party integrations and databases.

eferences

These are samples of websites I have built:

- https://Kemmie001.github.io/Resto/
- https://Kemmie001.github.io/John-coffe-shop/
- https://Kemmie001.github.io/IGTV./

